Well, first of all, hi, welcome. Uh, it
it's great to get together. I mean, I,
you know, I think you guys know I really
enjoy this. It's a chance to talk to the
fans, uh, just reflect on things and,
uh, sort of express my thoughts on where
we're at, where we're headed, where
we've been, and, um, um, you know, just
it's a great opportunity that we don't
manufacture. It's sometimes it's the
time of year where there's not a lot to
say. probably won't be able to answer a
lot of questions, but uh anyway, just to
get a feel for the owner's thoughts and
uh happy to, you know, listen to all
your questions. Um couldn't be more
excited about uh the upcoming season. We
are five months away, but uh I I I think
our plans are um really outstanding and
uh we're as I said by September I think
we'll uh be very thrilled with where
we're at and uh I I couldn't be more
excited about football. I miss it now. I
wish the off seasonason like half a
year. Are you kidding me? I mean uh I
feel it's a gift to have something
you're so in love with. Um, besides
people and dogs, uh, which is football
for me, I I just love the game. Uh, I
will watch every NFL game I can besides
the Eagles. I don't miss many other key
games. I'll watch them on tape. Uh, I
just, you know, since a little boy, I
love this sport. And it's a gift because
it's hard to find things that you're
just sort of unconditionally in love
with. So, um, I have that, um, I have it
for our team, and our city, and our
region. I know we've got the greatest
fans, but we also have a a franchise
that we're incredibly proud of and um we
hold ourselves to the highest
expectations. Uh it's very tough to
repeat. I I realize we were the
co-favorites going into this season with
I think 10 or 11% odds. Um you just, you
know, you have to sort of understand
uh what it is to be a co-f favorite.
Yeah, you've got a 10% chance. Um, but
we're we're that doesn't that doesn't
block us from thinking we've got a 100%
chance. I mean, we are gung-ho. Um, I
think we've got uh just outstanding
executives in our organization. Uh, you
know, I've got I'm very lucky to have
probably the best GM in the business,
outstanding team president, and Don
Sminsky. Everyone around. I mean, it's
just uh it's great for an owner to feel
you've got an incredible leadership
team, outstanding head coach, and uh all
all facets uh are really we demand it.
Um, but you know, if we're going to have
an area, whether it's AI, analytics, um,
marketing, um, autism foundation, we we
want to be the best and that's our goal
and we're willing to make changes that
will create and having the best people
work there. Um, speaking of just, you
know, it's not a an everyday question,
but our Eagles Autism Foundation, I
think, has evolved into the most
successful sports philanthropy, uh,
maybe in the world, but um, it's it's
really the way we choose what projects
to, um, invest in, uh, very dynamic
research projects, has attracted so much
capital from around the world and
investors. We just got an anonymous
check for $15 million because they
thought we did the best at evaluating
what exciting uh research projects to
invest in and they watched our process
and it's very scientific and it's um
it's very professional. And then we're
going to announce uh probably sometime
in April the first founding director of
the Lur Autism Institute uh at Chop and
Penn. And um I don't have to tell you, I
think Philadelphia will will be the
epicenter um for autism research in the
world. And uh there hasn't been a place
that's been a catalyst for all those
families and uh you know that that are
touched by autism around the world. So,
uh, if you're interested in supporting
research, the Lur Autism Institute will
will become, if it isn't already, an
epicenter and just in terms of funding
individual projects. Eagles Autism
Foundation. I always dreamed when I
bought the team that a sports
organization could be that influential
and dynamic and have that value. And
we've really achieved it. And, um, Ryan
Hammond, our executive director, is
incredible. It's just growing
geometrically and our players, everyone
in Philadelphia has just rallied around
it. So, I I know that's not on the top
of your mind for football questions, but
in terms of this owner, it's important
to me um and what we can accomplish
owning the team to both be as terrific a
steward of the franchise on the football
field, but also um you know, in the
community, the nation, and especially,
you know, around a condition like
autism.
Um, I guess that's uh, you know, I can
open up to any questions.
>> Jeffrey, um, the team did some
exploratory work on like focus groups
and such on a new stadium last year.
>> Yeah.
>> What if anything can you tell us at all
about, you know, the the team's pursuit
of the new stadium? I guess like in ter
what kind of stadium, where would it be?
Time frame I guess we all kind of assume
would be 2032.
>> Yeah, the lease is up in 2032. There's
extensions. Um, it's a long process.
When we researched Lincoln Financial
Field, it probably took us, I don't
know, two, three years of exploratory
research. Now, our exploratory research
is is is very much on looking at, uh,
stadiums around the world and
domestically. Um, is there anything we
can learn from Nashville and Buffalo?
Uh, is there anything we can learn from
the renovations in Madrid and Barcelona?
Um, it's really important. I think we
want to we want to maximize fan
amenities and attract the best possible
environment for um Philadelphia. And to
do that, you've really got to do the
exploratory research. Don't rush into
it. This is a big decision. Where's the
team going to be? So, um I I think it it
always pays off to take it slow. really
understand what's going on in the world
of design, fan amenities, uh artificial
intelligence in design, um what what
kind of facilities. So, it's really
exploratory. I wish I could give you
more permanent answers, but we're going
to take our time and I would hope in the
next year or two we'll we'll have some
more definitive approach to where we're
going. Jeff, Jeffrey, Jeffrey, last
season, um, you met with A, it was a
reported you met with AJ Brown on the
field regarding his frustration. I was
wondering what made you decide to do
that and as an owner, how do you decide
when it's time to, you know, come down
to the practice field and talk?
>> Ah, you know, I'm at practice a lot. Uh,
I I it's funny that was mentioned. I I
talk to players all the time. Uh, we go
out to dinners all the time. I mean,
people don't really know the the
relationship. It's a very close
relationship I have uh with our players
and uh I I've probably talked to AJ
whoever 30 times. Uh so that's it's just
I I feel like um at least with our
culture owner player relationships are
meant to be real, authentic and uh
interactive and warm and friendly pretty
much. That's uh that's the way I operate
and I think I always will. That's the
culture I want. So, if I have seen on a
on a field, it could be uh talking to
John Dorabos about his magic tricks or
AJ about the next game or whatever. It
never has to do with anything that's uh
particularly
relevant except uh it's a nice it's a
nice relationship that's not distant. On
the topic of the stadium exploration,
are there any non-negotiables
when you're you're thinking about a
stadium and as it pertains to, you know,
a roof or
anything like that?
>> No non-negotiables. We're so focused on
fan amenities. To me, that's uh the
number one thing, you know, just as a a
boy growing up, you want to have as best
a fan experience. The rest is
architecture, design, and where it ends
up. But uh no, it should just be a
wonderful fan experience and uh I don't
want to leave any stone unturned and
that's why we're doing the research. It
is interesting to to look at um you know
the Barcelonas, Madrids and other pretty
interesting renovations and of course
the new stadiums. Uh you learn every
time you're see a new stadium we're
going to learn from Nashville and
Buffalo and whatever else is Cleveland
maybe coming online and what their
design is. And uh I I think if you're
just humble about it and open that you
don't have all the answers and uh do the
exploratory work, you'll you'll end up
with a better long-term situation.
>> Jeffrey, you've had uh two players now
who go to the same company in Colombia
for stem cell therapy. What's your
understanding of that company, the
treatment that they are you facilitating
that at all?
>> I know nothing about it. I've read that
uh but you know um some of us uh do go
for stem cell treatments not me but some
some of us do go for stem cell
treatments in Canada and Europe and
stuff. Uh there's been a whole history
of uh of athletes and
patients going for uh PRP used to be
only in Europe. So, I think uh we're
we're not, you know, a party to that,
but uh everyone's entitled to figure out
solutions to their own ailments as we
all are.
>> You guys are normally proactive when it
comes to contracts and signing your core
players early. This seems like a good
window for Jaylen. Uh what what do you
uh how are you viewing that? Is that
something that you're you're active
with? And how do you see his future
here?
>> Right. It's it's our philosophy. It's
something also our philosophy never to
talk about it. So, uh, we we never ever
ever talk about as we're starting
negotiations with any player on
anything.
>> How about with his future in Philly? You
know, how do you feel about
>> he's he's a very good player and, uh,
I'm optimistic, but uh, we don't ever
discuss contracts uh, in in any way.
It's the best way to go.
>> Can I just How do you view his um, his
last season?
>> Good.
>> If I could follow up on that followup
>> there. Yeah. You know, a year ago after
the Super Bowl, you said, you know, he's
got a clutch gene and everything like
that.
>> Jaylen Herz. You're talking about
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. I think he was talking about
Jaylen Carter.
>> Jaylen Herz. I was
>> Oh, I thought you were about I I thought
it was all about Jaylen Carter.
>> Oh, Jaylen Herz. I'm I said Jaylen.
You're right. I should
>> I I was addressing it to about Jaylen
Carter.
>> So, yeah, if we can maybe
>> reverse it tape,
>> rewind it.
>> Yeah.
>> So, Jayen Herz,
>> we got a lot of Jaylen's around.
>> So, Jaylen Hertz, the same concept.
You're not gonna talk about contracts,
but how do you
>> He's under contract. Uh oh, I love
Jaylen. I mean, there's no bigger fan of
Jaylen than me. Uh Clutch Gene.
Absolutely. Uh you know, the guy MVP of
the Super Bowl 13 months ago, should
have been MVP of the Super Bowl right
before that against uh can against um
yeah, Kansas City the first time. Uh
exceptional and uh so dedicated. I mean,
I'm, you know, I think you probably
know, uh, spend a lot of time with
Jaylen and he's, uh, as I do with most
quarterbacks and, uh, incredibly
dedicated to the game, to winning and
being a huge winner and, uh, there's,
uh, I love everything about him. So,
anyway, uh, those things take
over time. We never would discuss it.
He's in the middle of a new contract
now. Yeah.
>> If I could have Sean.
>> Ah, Sean. Okay. Uh, yeah. incredibly
excited about the the offensive staff
that Nick has put together. It's a I I
tell you this is a real kudos to Nick to
recognize um what was clearly needed in
terms of our overall offensive
effectiveness. It's never about one
coach, one scheme, one staff or anything
like that. That's not the way we
operate. Um, we have our own proprietary
uh metrics and uh um ways of measuring
offensive defensive performance and our
offense was not uh what we were either
accustomed to or expectant of. And uh I
tell you Nick, one of the really great
qualities is his honesty about his own
staff and how he wants the best. And uh
great interview process, outstanding
process as it's been on in in some in
other cases. Um Sean,
incredibly impressive is all I'm going
to say. High high. You probably talk to
people here. Work ethic A+. Innovat
innoviveness and dynam dynamicism A+.
Um, I like to think and you never know,
we will see that uh we have a history of
finding young gems on offense and
defense. Um, starting, you know, back
with uh Gruden, Shawn Payeyton, Andy
Reid, especially the hiring of Andy as a
non-play caller. Um, and it just has
continued Shane, whatever. Uh, Kellen,
it's it's um I'm I'm incredibly excited
of the staff that Nick and Shawn put
together.
I'm sorry.
>> Was that um kind of following up on my
Jaylen Herz question, was a lot of the
changes with that coaching staff on
offense designed to kind of maximize
what he can do going forward?
>> It was designed to have us be a
championship offense. So, um, we had
just
12, what, 14 months ago, broken the
all-time NFL record for scoring in the
NFC Championship game in the Super Bowl.
So, uh, you know, think about that. In
the history of the NFL, no one had ever
scored more points in those two games, I
think. and then, you know, losing our
our offensive play caller to New Orleans
Saints, there's a human tendency
probably to keep at what you're doing as
opposed to understanding that maybe
other teams will catch on, uh, will do a
better job, maybe you're a little stale,
but in Knicks and and really the team's
defense, we just broken all records in
the history of the NFL in the
championship game and winning the Super
Bowl. So, it's a human it's a human
thing. Um, this year it was like really
um apparent to everybody, but especially
I would say to our head coach uh that we
were able and going to make some
significant offensive changes that would
get us back to being a championship
level offense. And uh it's and and it
resulted in a you know a patient
process. Um there's no speed in that
process that benefits you in the choice
of a coordinator or a head coach. Time
is a value and it's an asset. And
sometimes oh what are you doing? It's
taking no it's the opposite. Uh
certainly I think
the choice usually success gets more
correlated with patience and really
learning what coaches are out there and
what they're thinking and taking your
time. You also get the benefit of many
other interviewees on what's going on
with their uh teams and you learn a lot
about tendencies, what defenses are
doing to those schemes, what what uh
they're doing to attack advantages that
defenses are now gaining. You learn so
much in the process that a short
interview process whether it's for head
coach or any coordinator to me is a is
not how I would ever want to conduct it
unless you just happen to you know think
of one person you want which is rare. We
interviewed um a lot of people uh led by
Nick and what you would be amazed at is
the level of expertise of some of these
young coaches is extraordinary. The
league is very lucky. We've attracted so
many bright young people and it's uh
it's amazing to me to see it
and they're um and Sean's one of them.
Amazing.
>> As a follow that
>> there was during that process of you
guys searching for an offensive
coordinator. There was a sentiment out
there that maybe you know the building
was a reflection of how long it took you
guys to find somebody. What would you
say to those who would suggest that just
the opposite a good fit for
>> we are we are a a franchise I'm proud to
say a franchise and a culture that the
coaching fraternity loves around the
league. Uh so do the players. I mean
it's a place where you know you're going
to have a chance to compete for Super
Bowls. You know it's a very player
friendly culture. you know, the owner is
extremely uh emotionally involved and u
financially involved and in every way
involved and an incredible fan base and
uh it's it's yeah, I mean it's so like
it's a gift for us. We might as well
take advantage of that gift and that
reputation to learn what's going on with
you you see us play teams that are
pretty impressive, you know, offensively
or defensively. Why not find out what
what they're doing? We we have things
we've learned. Uh especially, you know,
Nick and the people that really
understand all the X's and O's. They
learned so much in the process. We
record the Zoom calls. Uh we can go
back. It's phenomenal. It's an
incredible asset. And if I were a fan
and knew what I know, I would want the
team to take as long as humanly possible
in those processes and pick the right
people. Don't pick the popular people
necessarily. Don't pick the oh the
leading candidates. They usually it
doesn't work out that way.
>> A year ago this time as about a possible
contract extension for for Nick Syriani.
I've given given it to him. How do you
how do you feel about that?
>> I feel great. Uh he's he's his
performance has been nothing short of
outstanding. One of the best first what
five years in the history of the NFL. Um
two Super Bowls in the last uh what
three years. Uh, one of which we won,
one of which we were taken away from us.
Uh, still bitter. Uh, you know, uh,
incredible uh, leadership. Um, but
authenticity is huge in my world. Um,
and in the players world. Um, nobody's
perfect. I'm far from it. You guys are
far from it. It's it's about
authenticity, leadership, understanding
when you should delegate, when you
shouldn't delegate, how to lead a team
through the ups and downs. We were the
only team to repeat as division
champions. No one else was even able to
do it. Uh in fact, in the NFC East, it's
been 20, we were the last team to do it,
right? 20 years ago.
Underrated to be able to even pull that
off. What happened to the other um what
is it? Seven division winners, they all
failed. Um, so it was disappointing not
to win the Super Bowl again. Hell yeah.
I mean, nobody is hurt more by it than
myself and our group, but uh I be
realistic. The guy's done a great job.
>> Nick, this time last year, you guys are
coming off winning the Super Bowl and
the push push was a really big topic
organization.
>> This time around, it seems there's no
attempt to stop it. I was wondering why
you think it's not getting as much
attention as it did last year.
>> Right. It was a pleasure to come here
and not have to fight. Uh, it was very
relaxed. I didn't have to bring Jason
Kelsey. Didn't have to explain the play.
I I didn't have to show how safe it is.
Data proves it out. Um maybe it helped
we didn't win the Super Bowl. I I don't
know what happened. Uh it's a very safe
play. I do know that because safety is
number one. Um and then, you know, we we
dialed down the effectiveness of it on
purpose. No, I'm just messing with you
guys. Uh we were not that good at it
also. And I and and I predicted that to
the league when we spoke to them about
maintaining the tush push. We said, you
know, defenses are going to adapt. There
is no play that is not stoppable,
including the tush push. And uh Buffalo
is way better at than we were uh this
year and uh the rest is history. I was
just it's a pleasure to come to an NFL
meet and I have to fight for something
so hard.
>> In discussing the stadium, you
referenced location. Yeah.
>> You've seen other teams cross state
lines, cross county lines. Is there um
consideration to move beyond South
Philadelphia?
>> Whatever is best for the fans. I mean,
we don't really go on a geographical
basis. It's whatever's best for the fans
and uh um you know, I can't tell you
where uh Cleveland is, Barcelona is. I I
don't know. It's just uh it's whatever.
Honestly, the bottom line is whatever's
best for the fans.
>> Going back to AJ Brown, uh the trade
talk, speculation has not subsided. That
would require a sign off from you, I
would imagine. Um, where are you with
that?
>> Yeah, as we kept saying AJ's an eagle
and uh he's uh he's definitely, you
know, I just will say this. Um, Devonte
and AJ, two great receivers and also
great teammates. I just want to say that
these two are um wonderful to have and
uh great teammates and great receivers.
Um so uh he's an eagle. Uh we'll see
what happens down the road, but uh so is
Devonte, so is Jaylen Herz, so is
Saquon. Uh they're all really great
competitors and uh luckily great
teammates and uh they just want to win
big.
>> Jeffrey, you've um green light the the
pushing forward of cash in future years
more than any other.
>> Yeah.
>> I guess maybe a little bit of a
reckoning the the last two offseason.
>> Not really. No, we're way above.
>> Yeah. Would you counter that? Is that Is
your philosophy still going to be
>> Yeah. I mean, this is where the uh the
emotional part probably gets in the way.
It's I can't help myself sometimes. It's
uh you know try to have every edge you
can and uh willing to spend the cash and
uh I think we have a chance to win
multiple more Super Bowls and uh you
know we're in this phase where um we
just want to there's nothing I want more
than that third Lombardi. uh last year
should have been the third Lombardi as I
said but uh I want to get that third
Lombardi and get it as soon as possible
and yet at the same time you know the
way we operate is we will very carefully
look at uh the midterm and the long term
because we want to set ourselves up for
sustained success. so hard in this
league with drafting towards the end,
uh, first place schedules, um, salary
cap, which, you know, makes you the
teams that are poor are going to be able
to spend more to get to the salary cap.
The teams that have an excess of star
players are not. So, um, we'll do
everything to maintain the the the
rosiness of the of the future, but at
the same time, we're gunning for that
third Lombardi. So, uh um in every way
possible,
>> are you anticipating playing
internationally in 2026? And if so,
where?
>> Great question. Uh we are not going to
give up a home game. We just did that in
Brazil. We did it early. Uh so we won't
be part of a cycle that has to give away
a home game in the near future, which is
was part of our plan of being in Sa
Paulo. Uh we are openly uh available to
be an away team. Um we think it's great
for spreading the Eagles and uh brand
and uh it's just it's it's an the league
is so um correctly directed and trying
to become more global. It's not that
easy for the NFL. Tackle football is not
played around the world the way
basketball is um and the way baseball is
in some places. So um yeah, we would be
able to be an away team um for you know
I don't know if it's going to happen.
They haven't told us, but we're we're
available. Uh, and we're also happy to
not be. It's just we're available. We
want to continue the push to
internationalize
recognizing at the same time. It's a
longhaul process honestly with the uh
tackle football. It's why flag football
probably has enormous potential. Um,
we're all invested in in a professional
flag team. We're invested in women
around the world playing flag. We're
invested in boys playing flag. Um, and
it's low cost. It's like uh basketball
in the sense it's it's almost like a
pickup game and uh it's taken off
incredibly. Uh it's going to be in the
LA Olympics. We hope to have it in the
Brisbane Olympics which will really
solidify it as a as a new global sport.
And how great to have um a a sport now
that could incorporate enormous numbers
of women and girls. Um it's fantastic
and it's in China. it's all over. So,
uh, I'm excited by that. It's it's, you
know, it's part of, I think, a good
strategy for the NFL. It's good for the
NFL to run a pro league. Um, and we've
got, you know, pretty well-healed
investors in it. And, um, it's always
it's always been an issue because the
games that are pickup with just a ball
are a lot easier to translate. Amid the
coaching uh staff changes this
offseason, Jeff Stoutland walking away.
How do you reckon with you moving
forward with a new offense? Yeah, new
staff members, but also
>> not having someone who is so integral
and that successful
>> Stout um I think you guys know uh sees
like family to us uh literally. And so,
um, we we still talk all the time and
it's just, uh, you know, it's a it's a
it's it's a wonderful it's been a
wonderful relationship that will
continue. And, uh, it's, um,
he's a he's just a a wonderful person
and, uh, has a wonderful family and, uh,
we all maintain very, very close ties
with Stout. It's it's um, Sean's offense
um, you know, that they Nick and he put
together. I'm so impressed with the
people that they've put together as well
uh all over. And uh by the way, that's
another advantage of the of the
interview process is you find others
that could become
superb coaches in what you're trying to
do uh that were finalists for the
position. And you know, in some cases,
we were lucky to be able to uh hire them
to be assisting with Shawn. Shawn picked
them. Uh, and so it was uh that's
another advantage of of really doing
your due diligence.
>> Julian has had an official role now for
a while. Y is there any more thought to
a a plan of him ramping up duties,
responsibilities? Is there any kind of
timeline
>> there? There's no timeline, but I love
the way it's been going. Um, he's, you
know, quite involved in the business
operations, the football operations, uh,
philanthropic operations, marketing. uh
he's getting a great great um sort of
feel for everything. Um and that that's
the best way to do it. It's not to speed
it up. Um on on my own behalf, uh maybe
I still have a lot of gray hair, but I
am probably more involved than ever,
ironically. Uh
it's interesting. I think since co
probably I benefit more from the the
ability to interact with my executives.
uh on Zoom and things like that. I I if
I were to total the involvement then
before COVID and now I would say I'm
probably more involved now but less
physically have to be at uh now called
Jefferson Health Complex. Uh I so it's
it's kind of a funny thing. It's it's
it's not that it's behind the scenes.
It's very overt. But I will talk to my
executives more often uh and probably
with more intensity because I have uh a
son that's growing and learning
everything and so he can both watch how
focused and intense I am still and yet
at the same time learn from all the the
executives we have. I you know I don't
have to tell you we've had some of the
same outstanding senior executives for
almost a quarter a century. our team
president is really one of the best in
sports. Our GM I think is definitely one
of the best in sports and um he's he's
been around a lot of really top
executives. Um, so it's an ideal
learning environment and you're right,
it's it it it ramps up slowly, but it's
not sort of counter to my own
involvement because uh I listen, if you
want to live a long time, I was always
told, don't ever retire and uh keep that
intensity going. And I abs I love owning
the Eagles. I love trying to make us
even better in every way. And u and
that's what I'm focused on. That's why
my energy is high. And uh I I can't tell
you the times like 4 in the morning I'll
wake up and I'm thinking is Howie up?
You know uh should we text on something?
Could be a long snapper could be totally
uh something crazy for 26 27 uh or
something right now. You know who's
going to be our fourth at this position?
I worry a lot. So uh I love having that
love of of what we're trying to do.
>> On the topic of the practice Yeah.
Exactly.
>> On the topic of the practice facility.
Yeah. It's it's over 20 years old now.
Yeah.
>> I I know you thought it was integral
part of the organization when you
Absolutely.
>> Uh it's come up in the NFL PA surveys,
>> what are your thoughts on on kind of the
future of that facility?
>> Listen, if we um so yeah, I mean it's
it's also the stadium. I love our
stadium. Lincoln Financial Field's
wonderful. It will be um once
Washington's built the oldest stadium in
the division. That doesn't mean there's
any negative to that. You know, there's
Fenway, there's Lambo, whatever.
There's no question our practice
facility and our uh our and our
particularly our stadium uh will be the
oldest in the division. Um we have put
so much money into the stadium so it
doesn't like appear that way and it's
still great and people still love it but
uh it's it's a fact of that exploration
I was talking to you about. Do we want
to be uh you know in 2045 15 years older
than uh every other stadium in our
division or whatever? I we'd have to
see. Uh maybe uh but that it's all part
of it. I know part of our culture is to
be incredibly supportive of um to
maximize the athletic ability that we
have um of our players, our coaches, and
everybody. That will always be the top
priority. So whatever we're doing with
stadium, with practice facility, uh if
it's not, you know, near top-notch, it's
not uh our goal. we always want to be as
I you know I think we pioneered that we
went from worst to probably best uh when
we did um what was then Novaare so it
it'll still be the philosophy it's got
to be the best we are hellbent on things
that probably don't get talked about a
lot but it's not so much physical as it
is things like preventive health data uh
injury prevention um genetic testing um
there there's so much that we try to
employ that we hope gives us an edge at
times. You know, we want to try to enter
the playoffs um assuming we make the
playoffs uh as healthy as we can. We do
play the long game at times. We won't
short uh shorten um our uh ability to
have a player play. We we are more
conservative. We want we play the long
game. And uh but a lot of that goes into
what do we do data-wise to give us the
best odds of having as few injuries as
possible and timeliness of those
injuries as well. It's a big part of it.
It's not just the physical um building
which is important too, but it's it's
what you're doing with your data and
what are you trying to accomplish. We
want to be as healthy as possible
entering into uh December, January,
February.
recent success, your recent success has
raised expectations for franchise. Yes.
>> Uh you know, obviously you have one of
the more passionate fan bases. Uh but
sometimes that has crossed over the
line. You saw the tool as well.
>> Yeah. Unfortunately.
>> So when that when that brings about
certain types of criticism, how do you
manage that versus, you know, your own
high expectations as well, especially
going into this season?
>> Yeah.
>> Considering all that you guys have
accomplished.
>> A great question. the more you succeed,
the higher your own expectations are,
the higher your the fan expectations
are. Um, the NFL is uniquely built to to
defeat that. And we think we're
hopefully able to organize in a way we
can defeat their ability uh to make
things so equal. Do you know what I
mean? It's sort of like a it's a funny
thing. Uh the league thrives because of
the ability of teams to go from third or
fourth place to first place. Uh the
draft certainly favors those that are up
at the top five every year. Uh a lot
goes into the scheduling. You're on a
first place schedule. Uh the way I
manage it is um you know I I'm just like
our I'm sort of you know it's like our
fans. I'm hellbent on getting another
championship. Expectations. It's not
going to happen every year. It's damn
tough to repeat. But uh why not try to
do everything possible? Um, you know, I
can't be more excited about next
September and uh it's just my
expectations are always been be world
class, at least try to be world class at
everything. And um where you're not at
all, be self-critical at all times where
you're not able to do what you hope to
do. So, uh we didn't win the Super Bowl
this past February. We won it the year
before. What did we do? You know, be
self-critical. That's it's always an
advantage as a human being. How are you
as a you know a father, a husband, a dog
owner, whatever it is. Uh be be real. Be
real.
>> So kind of along those lines, like you
lost five starters on defense after the
Super Bowl, three, you know, this past
month and everything. Y
>> you know, you have a whole bunch of
young guys on defense ready to kind of
step in who have stepped in. Yes.
>> They're going to be up for second
contracts. I mean, does that kind of
like signify why it's so hard to repeat
because you constantly have to lose
players, try to replace?
>> Yeah, the salary cap is at the average
of expenditures in the uh, you know, a
certain percentage of revenues in the
NFL. So, if you draft really well,
you're going to have way more the value
of an average team's expenditures in
value. So, Milton Williams, great
player. How are we going to afford to
keep Milton Williams when we have uh you
know Jordan Davis, Jaylen Carter, uh
Mororrow JO? You just have to you have
to get the compensatory pick if you can
plan it that way. But what it does and
how he's literally the best at it in the
NFL is it gives you a strategy of it's
going to force you to do certain things
on offense. uh to know that you're going
to have some young really great stars
coming up on defense uh that you want to
keep. So, we've always done, you know, a
reasonably good job of identifying who
those core terrific players are. Try to
sign them early if you can. And then as
you're doing that, know those are the
expenditures you're suddenly going to
have on defense. What are you gonna do
on offense to sort of uh counter that in
a way where you're getting better young
talent on first contracts on offense?
And you know, I would say that Howie's
as good as it gets on that strategy, but
you do you don't want it to be random.
You want to plan for it, and that's what
we do. Um very directly plan for it. So
uh uh because you know that's going to
happen. We don't want to ever be in a
position of a key key core player and
not be able to resign them. At least try
early. It's uh it's just, you know,
being smart about it.
>> All right.
>> Okay.
>> You good?
>> Hope you're good. Yeah. Okay. Great
getting together, you guys.